askhelpbox.com 2014-07-15

# Ask Help Box - Privacy Policy

Our visitors privacy is critically important to us. Askhelpbox is guided by some basic ideeas:

  * We don't ask you for personal information because we simply don't need it :)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Askhelpbox collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Askhelpbox’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Askhelpbox’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Askhelpbox may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Askhelpbox also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on WordPress.com blogs. Askhelpbox only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Askhelpbox’s websites choose to interact with Askhelpbox in ways that require Askhelpbox to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Askhelpbox gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Askhelpbox collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Askhelpbox. Askhelpbox does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Askhelpbox may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to the websites. For instance, Askhelpbox may monitor the most popular searches on askhelpbox.com. Askhelpbox may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Askhelpbox does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Askhelpbox discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Askhelpbox’s behalf or to provide services available at Askhelpbox’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Askhelpbox’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Askhelpbox will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Askhelpbox discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Askhelpbox believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Askhelpbox, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Askhelpbox website and have supplied your email address, Askhelpbox may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Askhelpbox and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Askhelpbox takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Askhelpbox uses cookies to help Askhelpbox identify and track visitors, their usage of Askhelpbox website, and their website access preferences. Askhelpbox visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Askhelpbox’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Askhelpbox’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Askhelpbox and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Askhelpbox may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Askhelpbox’s sole discretion. Askhelpbox encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a WordPress.com account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Last Updated on _April 18, 2014_
